Card.create(front: "That guy from the thing", back: "Justin", score: 0)
Card.create(front: "If we have data, let's look at data. If all we have are opinions, let's go with mine.", back: "Jim Barksdale, former CEO of Netscape", score: 0)
Card.create(front: "Science says charisma is the combination of... (Scott Adams)", back: "Power and empathy", score: 0)
Card.create(front: "Are you my appendix?", back: "Because I've got this strange feeling in my gut that I should take you out", score: 0)
Card.create(front: "Hanlon's Razor", back: "Never attribute to malice what can be explained by stupidity", score: 0)
Card.create(front: "I don't look at a man who is an expert in one area as a specialist... (Conor McGregor)", back: "I look at him as a rookie in ten other areas.", score: 0)
Card.create(front: "Men of lofty genius... (Leonardo DaVinci)", back: "When they are doing the least work are the most active", score: 0)
Card.create(front: "Ten-dollar words disguise  ______ (Tim Ferris)", back: "Imprecision", score: 0)
Card.create(front: "Vision without execution is...", back: "Hallucination (Thomas Edison)", score: 0)
Card.create(front: "The real purpose of the scientific method is...", back: "To make sure that Nature hasn't misled you into thinking you know something that you actually don't. (Robert Pirsig)", score: 0)
Card.create(front: "It isn't _______ that wears you out, it's _________", back: "Muhammad Ali", score: 0)
Card.create(front: "Intelligence should be viewed as...", back: "A physical process that maximizes future freedom of action, and minimizes restraint of action. (Alex Wissner Gross)", score: 0)
